{
    "subject": "resource/Russel_Walder",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Russel Walder's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9465144276618958,
            "question": "Does Russel Walder currently live in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.911054790019989,
            "question": "What is the name of Russel Walder's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9013368487358093,
            "question": "Is Russel Walder originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8857176303863525,
            "question": "What country is Russel Walder's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8284987807273865,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Russel Walder's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7910386919975281,
            "question": "If Russel Walder was born outside the United States, where else might he be from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7319623231887817,
            "question": "How has Russel Walder's hometown influenced him?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6850290894508362,
            "question": "Where is Russel Walder from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6320133805274963,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of life in Russel Walder's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31286612153053284,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Russel Walder's place of birth?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Russel Walder's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9022_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of life in Russel Walder's hometown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9022_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Russel Walder from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9022_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Russel Walder's hometown influenced him?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9022_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9022_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the statement \"Russel Walder's hometown is United States\" is supported by the documents:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe document mentions that \"Walder was born and raised in Deerfield, Illinois\", which implies that his hometown is indeed Deerfield, Illinois, not the United States as a whole."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Russel Walder was born and raised in Deerfield, Illinois, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Russel Walder's hometown is United States\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information states that Russel Walder was born and raised in Deerfield, Illinois, which is a specific location within the United States.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}